Contact

dorcas.apata@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dorcasmotunrayo-ayanga-msn-rn-cnlccrn-cphq-964632168 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care Nursing
Patient Safety
Nursing Education

Dorcas Motunrayo Ayanga MSN RN CNL CCRN CPHQ

Critical Care RN

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Reviewer with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Nursing Education, Patient Safety, Electronic Medical Record (EMR), and Home Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a MS Nursing focused in Clinical Nurse Leader from University of Maryland Baltimore.

Experience

CHI St. Luke's Health - Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center CV Recovery Nurse
June 2019 - Present (1 year)
Houston, TX

Recover and stabilize post op heart surgery patients.

Memorial Hermann Health System Lead Clinical Quality Reviewer June 2018 - June 2019 (1 year 1 month) Houston, Texas Area

Quality, Clinical Education, Patient Safety & Risk (Home Based Services), Yellow Belt Healthcare

Harris Health System
Quality Management Coordinator
May 2017 - April 2018 (1 year)
Houston, Texas Area

Critical Care, Mother-Baby

CHI St. Luke's Health - Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center Clinical Education Specialist June 2016 - March 2017 (10 months)

Houston, Texas Area

CV Recovery Nurse and Nurse Education Specialist

Wake Forest Baptist Health
Critical Care RN
June 2012 - May 2016 (4 years)
Greensboro/Winston-Salem, North Carolina Area

CTICU/CCU

DaVita Kidney Care Charge Nurse June 2010 - May 2012 (2 years) Baltimore, Maryland Area

Charge Nurse

Education

Texas Woman's University AG-ACNP · (2017)

University of Maryland Baltimore

MS Nursing, Clinical Nurse Leader · (2008 - 2010)

University of Maryland Baltimore County

BSc Interdisciplinary Studies , Biology and Aging Studies · (2005 - 2007)

Baltimore City Community College
Associate of Arts and Sciences - AAS, General Science · (2003 - 2005)

Lagos State University
(2000 - 2003)